You know, the sales order agent can can
process incoming emails and you already
configured it in this Business Central
instance. So, now it monitors shared
inbox and does it work? Oh, I can see
that something is already
processed and received.
But what if some of my customers are in
parallel sending mails to my personal
inbox?
How can I do How can I solve this
problem? With this release, you can
actually have several sales order agents
running in parallel and you have access
to both of them.
Let's do Let's do that. So, now
I activating the second sales order
agent and it proposed display name sales
order agent two, but we can use
something else. For example, that would
be me. It would be my agent. It would be
looking to a different uh
email.
The current user.
And again, reminder that is very good
idea to select a dedicated folder
uh to make sure that uh sales order the
agent is not picking up absolutely every
email you received and which lands in
your inbox.
All right. The next thing I want to do
is probably to customize it. Maybe I
want to decide uh if I want to review
uh incoming messages or not.
Which might be a good idea if you
decided to keep inbox uh as a default
one. Do I send quotes or orders and if I
want to review created document before
uh allowing sales order agent to draft a
reply.
All these settings are here. Definitely,
what I want to do, I want to have a
custom signature.
Let me change it.
Custom signature.
I'm activating this agent and I'm
waiting
to get new emails.
Let's activate the sales order agent.
Sales order agent active. Now I can see
that there are two of them.
And the second one, which looks at my
inbox, already get the new message.
Probably it's time for me to review it.
I'm going to review it.
And this time it actually arriving from
the customer which I never work with.
His email is unknown@contoso.com.
Previously, what we do in these cases,
we created contact on the fly, right
from here. With this version, we have
options. We can actually decide to use a
different existing contact, maybe once,
which can be useful if we really receive
emails via some portal from no-reply or
shared inboxes.
Or if we know that customer got a new
email address, but this customer already
exist in Business Central, we can
actually update the customer
information.
All right, I will pick existing
customer,
Crystal York,
and update email address with a new one.
And confirm.
And let the sales order agent to do its
job.
Here I can see both uh
agents running in parallel. I can see
different statistics and I can navigate
and switch between one or another.
So now I can actually add even more
sales order agents if I have multiple
shared inbox or maybe I need to monitor
something for my colleagues while they
are out on vacation. If you have not set
up sales order agent yet,
check the video with the details on how
you can do it.